# CAROLINA WONG

# GRAPHIC DESIGNER

# PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

Graphic Designer with 8 years of experience in the management of the complete design process, from conceptualization to delivery of the final product. Expert in Print and Marketing Advertising. Knowledgeable in all stages of print production from substrate to delivery methods. Skilled in Adobe Creative Suite (Photoshop, InDesign, Illustrator, Dreamweaver, Lightroom, Bridge), Microsoft Office (Word, Excel, Powerpoint, Office) and web design programs (HTML, CSS, WordPress). Ability to communicate effectively and understand what clients are looking for and developing solutions that match their needs. Able to work efficiently under pressure and within tight deadlines.

### EXPERIENCES

#### CONTRACT GRAPHIC DESIGNER

Outsource Marketing, White Rock, BC

April 2016-Present

- · Developing aspects of proposal design, development and pre-print production
- Creating complex graphics and illustrations, differentiating proposal submissions, corporate brochures and company branding
- · Ensuring high quality and timely submissions that address all proposal requirements
- · Accurately building and managing the InDesign from project initiation through to print production

#### CONTRACT GRAPHIC DESIGNER

Southpointe Academy, Tsawwassen, BC

May 2015-Present

- Developing and designing all marketing collateral such as, but not limited to, the Annual Report, newspaper ads, banners, posters, promotional brochures and pamphlets, school prospectus
- · Maintaining and updating the school website via WordPress and CSS

# **GRAPHIC DESIGNER**

**QE Home Decor**, Burnaby, BC

January 2015 – January 2016

- Maintaining all aspects of packaging from concept, design, redesign, updating information, photoshopping
  to preflight production and coordinating with our international offices
- Creating and executing web related duties, including creating and deploying e-blasts, and designing collateral for social media across multiple platforms
- $\bullet \ \ Photographing \ new \ products, including \ set \ up \ and \ take \ down \ of \ sets \ and \ post \ production \ work$

#### **GRAPHIC DESIGNER**

#### Northland Properties, Vancouver, BC

June 2014-November 2014

- Developing and designing all marketing materials for all Sutton Place, Signature and Sandman Hotels such as advertising print collaterals, magazines, rack cards, brochures, flat sheets and all in-house communication materials
- · Designing and deploying all e-blasts, maintaining websites for all hotels under Northland Properties
- Developing and designing special projects for the President of Sandman Hotel Group such as logos, presentations and reports

#### GRAPHIC DESIGNER / MARKETING ASSISTANT

#### Edgewater Casino, Vancouver, BC

2012-2014

- Designing and optimizing all marketing collateral such as promotions, advertisements, posters, and signage
  for multiple platforms as well as for large and small print formats
- · Laying out the direct mailers, coupons, deploying e-blasts and updating the Casino's websites

# CONTACTS



me@carolinawong.com



www.carolinawong.com

#### EDUCATION

# GRAPHIC DESIGN & FOUNDATIONS FOR DESIGN

Art Institute of Vancouver, Vancouver, BC 2010–2012

# BACHELORS IN FINE ARTS IN VISUAL ARTS

University of British Columbia, Vancouver, BC 2006–2010

Specialization in Print Media, Digital Media and Photography

#### SKILLS

- Adobe Creative Suite
  - Photoshop
  - InDesign
  - Illustrator
  - Dreamweaver
  - Lightroom
  - Bridge
- Microsoft Office
  - Word
  - Excel
  - Powerpoint
  - Office
- HTML & CSS, jQuery
- User Interface
- · Drawing & Painting
- Illustration
- Handlettering / Typography
- Studio Lighting & Photography
- Photography Manipulation
- Bi-lingual
  - English
  - Chinese

# REFERENCES

Available Upon Request